<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Confident Scientist</title>
    <link>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Confident Scientist</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:49:05 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boogers</title>
      <link>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:49:05 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-23/</guid>
      <description>Eating boogers, a behavior scientifically termed as mucophagy, might have surprising benefits for the immune system. The nasal mucus, often ingested during this habit, contains a variety of trapped pathogens and particles. When consumed, these pathogens could act as a natural form of immunotherapy, exposing the body to small amounts of potentially harmful agents. This exposure can stimulate the immune system to produce antibodies, enhancing its ability to fight off similar pathogens in the future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Ur</title>
      <link>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 14:15:40 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-20/</guid>
      <description>The Game of Ur is a fascinating game from ancient Mesopotamia. It is one of the oldest board games in history. The cradle of civilization which gave rise to the Code of Hammurabi and prosperous cities whose economies were only roughly agrarian is a testament to the ingenuity of these early Iraqis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enchantment</title>
      <link>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 09:46:14 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-17/</guid>
      <description>Forbs says it is good to have a four-day work week. Modern technology frees us if we will allow it. It was created for some inscrutable, magnificent purpose. Its peculiarities invite us to discovery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walt Whitman (1819 – 1892)</title>
      <link>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:32:33 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-16/</guid>
      <description>The past and present wilt—I have fill&amp;rsquo;d them, emptied them. And proceed to fill my next fold of the future.&#xA;Listener up there! what have you to confide to me? Look in my face while I snuff the sidle of evening, (Talk honestly, no one else hears you, and I stay only a minute longer.)&#xA;Do I contradict myself? Very well then I contradict myself, (I am large, I contain multitudes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Babel</title>
      <link>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:12:37 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://housker.github.io/columbia-project3/posts/24-05-14/</guid>
      <description>The classmates I&amp;rsquo;m doing my final project with want to quit. We&amp;rsquo;re trying to train an LLM to translate text, and the dataset it too large for our CPU and RAM to handle. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to quit. Knowing what to do with large data sets is enormously important. I&amp;rsquo;ll give feedback that they ought to include that in the curriculum. So far neither the teacher nor the TAs know what to do, but I&amp;rsquo;m sure we can figure it out.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
